<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <origin/>
                <pubdate>20160401</pubdate>
                <title>Maryland Property Data - Tax Map Grids</title>
                <onlink>http://geodata.md.gov/imap/rest/services/PlanningCadastre/MD_PropertyData/MapServer/2</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>This layer contains the boundaries and IDs of the Maryland tax maps produced by Maryland Department of Planning. Tax maps, also known as assessment maps, property maps or parcel maps, are a graphic representation of real property showing and defining individual property boundaries in relationship to contiguous real property.This is a MD iMAP hosted service layer. Find more information at https://imap.maryland.gov.Feature Service Layer Link:https://geodata.md.gov/imap/rest/services/PlanningCadastre/MD_PropertyData/MapServer/2</abstract>
            <purpose>Maryland Property Data - Tax Map Grids</purpose>
        </descript>
        <status>
            <update>As needed</update>
        </status>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Residential</themekey>
                <themekey>Parcel</themekey>
                <themekey>Points</themekey>
                <themekey>Property</themekey>
                <themekey>View</themekey>
                <themekey>Cadastral</themekey>
                <themekey>MDP</themekey>
                <themekey>aryland Department of Planning</themekey>
                <themekey>State Department of Assessments and Taxation</themekey>
                <themekey>Vector</themekey>
                <themekey>Tax</themekey>
                <themekey>Maps</themekey>
                <themekey>Grids</themekey>
                <themekey>ID</themekey>
                <themekey>Raster</themekey>
                <themekey>Dynamic</themekey>
                <themekey>WMS</themekey>
                <themekey>Maryland</themekey>
                <themekey>State</themekey>
                <themekey>MD iMAP</themekey>
                <themekey>KML</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>The Spatial Data, and the information therein, (collectively the "Data") is provided "as is" without warranty of any kind, either expressed, implied, or statutory. The user assumes the entire risk as to quality and performance of the Data. No guarantee of accuracy is granted, nor is any responsibility for reliance thereon assumed. In no event shall the State of Maryland be liable for direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or special damages of any kind. The State of Maryland does not accept liability for any damages or misrepresentation caused by inaccuracies in the Data or as a result to changes to the Data, nor is there responsibility assumed to maintain the Data in any manner or form. The Data can be freely distributed as long as the metadata entry is not modified or deleted. Any data derived from the Data must acknowledge the State of Maryland in the metadata.</useconst>
        <datacred>MD iMAP, MDP</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20180214</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
